Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1965-2007; Accession 2009-M-018
  - Correspondence
    - Moore, Aideen, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Moore v. Regents of California, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Moreno, Jonathan, 1991-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
    - Morgenstern, Lewis, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Morillo, Arturo, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Morriem, E. Haavi, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Most, John, 1989-1998 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Multiple Sclerosis Society, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Murray, Tom, 1981-2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Musto, David, 1976-1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Nadel, Ethan, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Naegel, Gary, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Naftolin, Fred, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Nark, Julie, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Nathan, David, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Nathan, Viswa, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - National Action Plan on Breast Cancer (NAPBC), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - National Advisory Board on Ethics in Reproduction, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - National Bioethics Advisory Committee, 1996-2000 (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
      - Comments on "Research Involving Subjects with Mental Disorders That May Affect Decisionmaking Capacity", 1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - National Center for Complementary and Alternative Medicine (NCCAM)/placebo, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - National Center for Health Statistics (NCHS), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - National Emphysema Treatment Trial (NETT), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
    - National Eye Institute (NEI) Collaborative Ocular Melanoma Study (COMS), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute (NHLBI)
      - Lung DSMB, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Magnesium in Coronaries (MAGIC), 1998-2002 (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
      - NETT, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID) HIVNET, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), 1998-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - DSMB, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
      - Hsiao, John, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Human Subjects Research Council Workgroup, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Street, Linda, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - National Science Foundation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - New England Journal of Medicine (NEJM), 1992, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
      - Letter, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - New Haven Register, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - New York State, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - New York Times, 1984-1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Letter, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Needle, Richard, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Nelkin, Dot, 1982-1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Newman, Rick, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Newton, Lisa, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
    - Ngugi, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Nicholson, Richard, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Nightingale, Stuart, 1982-1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Nobel Committee, 1976-2000 (Box 13, Folder 27-28)
    - Nolan, Kathleen, 1978-1993 (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
    - Norris, Deborrah, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 31-33)
    - Novick, Alvin, 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Nuland, Sherwin, 1979-1996 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Nuremberg Conference, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Nursing, School of, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - O'Connell, Larry, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Office for Protection from Research Risks (OPRR), 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Search, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Office of AIDS Reseach, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Office of Human Research Protections, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ohnuki-Tierney, Emiko, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Oldham, John M., 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Olsen, Douglas, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
    - Oral History Association, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ort, Sharon, 1989-1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Osias, Brian, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Osler Lecture, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Outka, Gene, 1976-1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Page, Roy, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Pain, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Palmer, Bill, 1981-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Pan American Health Organization (PAHO), 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 19-21)
    - Papac, Rose, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Pardes, Herb, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Paris, John, 1985-1990 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Park, Patricia, 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Partnership for a Drug-Free America, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Patterson, Amy, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Patterson, Helaine, 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Payer, Lynn, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
    - Pedersen, Tove, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Pediatric AIDS Conference, Yale, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Pediatric AIDS Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 32-33)
    - Pediatric Ethics Committee, 1991-2000 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Peduzzi, Peter, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Pelligrino, Ed, 1975-1985 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Pence, Gregory, 1979-1992 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Pennsylvania (University of) Project, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Perrow, Charles, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Periodontology, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Peterson, Curt, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Peterson, Lynn, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association (PMA), 1984 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - The Pharos, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Philadelphia Association for Clinical Trials (PACT), 1981-1991 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Phillips, Don, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Philosopher's Index, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Pilon, Susan, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Pimple, Ken, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Pinn, Vivian, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 52-53)
    - Plotnikoff, Greg, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Polmar, Suzanne, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Porter, Lane, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Post, Stephen, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Powderly, Kathleen, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Pranulis, Mary Ann, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Advisory Committee on the Gulf War, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Prichard, James W., 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Pritam Krishna Shrestha, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Professional Responsibility (PR) course, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Death/dying lecture, 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Program for Study of Health Care Relationships, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Prusoff, Bill, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Public Responsibility in Medicine and Research (PRIM&R), 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 9-13)
      - 101, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMC), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
      - Central Review Boards (CRB), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Health Policy, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Purtilo, Ruth, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Qiu, Ren-Zong, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Quagliarello, Vincent, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Quality of Life Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Quality of Life Research, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Rachlin, Joan, 1983-1993 (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
    - Radiation Experiments, Advisory Committee on Human, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
    - Ramalingaswami, V., 1998 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Rapport, Richard, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Rastegar, Asghar, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Rathbone, Rodian, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Ratzan, Richard, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Rawls, John, 1973-1976 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Reich, Warren, 1976-1995 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Reiser, Stan, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Relationships, Health Care, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Religion Index One, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Relman, Arnold, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Rettig, Richard, Undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Richard, Alison, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Rifkin, Dena, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Ritchie, Al, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Ritchie, J. M., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Rivlin, Richard, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Roberts, Laura, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
    - Robertson, J. A., 1979-1999 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Robinson, Dorothy, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Rodriguez-Torres, Ramon, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Rose, Susan, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Rosenberg, L. E., 1971-1989 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Rosenthal, Robert, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Rossip, Martin, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Rothenberg, Karen, 1993, undated (Box 15, Folder 54-55)
    - Rothenberg, Leslie, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Rothman, David, 1980-1993 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Rothman, Sheila, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Rothstein, Julie, 1991-2000 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Royal Palace, Undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Rozovsky, Fay, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Ruddich, Bill, Undated (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Russia, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Ruwe, Stacy, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Ryan, Ken, 1976-1995 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Saberski, Lloyd, 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Sachs, Fred, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Sacks, Herbert: Agency for International Development (AID), 1973-1992 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Sacks, Kate, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Sales, Bruce D., 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Sanders, Charles, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Sandomire, Hazel, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Santelli, John, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Sanyal, Mrinal, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Sartorelli, Alan C., 1999 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Sastrowijoto, Soenarto, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Sawin, Charles, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Schaffner, Kenneth, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Scheinfeld, Noah, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Schell Center for International Human Rights, 1990-1993 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
    - Schensul, Jay, 1997-2002 (Box 16, Folder 13-15)
    - Schetky, Diane, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Schuck, Peter, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Schwab-Stone, Mary, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, Ilsa, 1992-1995 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Schwartz, Peter, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Science and Medicine, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Scocozza, Lone, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Selwitz, Ada Sue, 1991-2000 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
    - Selwyn, Peter, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Selzer, Richard, 1976, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Seminars in Health Policy and Delivery (SHPD), 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 27-28)
    - Senior Faculty Associates, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Serle, Janet, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Sethy, Vimala, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Shamoo, Adil, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Shapiro, Harold, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Sharon, Amy, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Sheehe, Paul, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Shelton, Jim, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Shipp, Allan, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Short, E. M., 1975-1987 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Sidel, Victor, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Siegel, Bernard, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Siegler, Mark, 1978-1995 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Silver, Arnold, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Singer, Peter, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 43-44)
    - Sjoerdsma, Albert, 1979-2001 (Box 16, Folder 45-46)
    - Skelly, William, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Slayman, Carolyn, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Slifka Center, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Smith, Clyde (Lanny), 1993 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Smith, David H., 1994-2004 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Smith, Gaddis, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Smith, Nathan, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Smits, Helen, 1975-1995 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Snyder, Ed, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 55-56)
    - Society for Bioethics Consultation (SBC), 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 57-58)
    - Society for Clinical Trials, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Society for Health and Human Values, 1983-1996 (Box 16, Folder 60-61)
    - Society for the Right to Die, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Solbakk, Jan Helge, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 63-64)
    - Solberg, Mary, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Solomon, Rachel, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Somerville, Margaret, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 67-68)
    - Sonis, Jeffrey, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 69-70)
    - Sonnenreich, Michael R., 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Sontag, Susan, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Soros: Open Society Institute, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - South Carolina, Medical University of, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Spangler, Stephanie, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Spicer, Carol, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Spiers, Herb, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Spilker, Bert, 1992-1998 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Spinsanti, Sandro, 1991-1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Spiro, H. M., 1972-1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Stambler, Moses, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Starzl, Tom, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Stein, Gary, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Stein, Robert, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Stevens, Robert B., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Stoch, Aubrey, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Stoller, J. K., 1979-1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Stowe, Bruce B., Dr., 1967 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Straus, Marc, 1980-1993 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Street, Lynn, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Stryker, Jeff, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Sugarman, Jeremy, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Sutherland, Scott, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Swartz, Morton, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Swazey, Judith, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Swenson, Sara, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Szapocznik, José, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Talcott, James, 1978-1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Tan, S. Y., 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Taver, Carol A., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Taylor, Stephanie, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Teague, Barbara, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Tedesco, Laurie (Spiro), Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Telectronics, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Thesis information, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Thier, S. O., 1975-1995 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Think Pad, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Thomas, Ned, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Thomasma, David D., 1986-2000 (Box 17, Folder 39-40)
    - Tignor, Gregory, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Tischenko, Pavel, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Toulmin, Stephen, 1975-1992 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Towe, Annie, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Truog, Robert, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Tsumura Company, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 46-48)
    - Twomey, John G., 1999 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - United Nations Programme on HIV/AIDS (UNAIDS), 1998 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - United States Pharmacopeia (USP), 1994 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) Schizophrenia Study, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Urquhart, John, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Vaidya, Ashok B., 1966-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Vallvé, Carles, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Vanderpool, Harold, 1985-1996 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
    - Van Dusen, Annie, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Van Italie, Tina, Circa 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - VaxGen, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
    - Velasco-Suarez, Manuel, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Vermont State Medical Society, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Vesel, Tamara, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Vieira, Sonia, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Vinicky, Janicemarie, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Volandes, Angelo, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
    - Walker, Richard, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Walker, Stuart, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Wardell, Bill, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Warshaw, Joseph, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Watkins, Judith, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Waxman, Merle, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Webster, George, 1991-1999 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Weed, Matthew, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Wei, Marlynn, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Weicker, Lowell, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Weijer, Charles, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Weiner, Charles, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Wells, Hillary, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Wessell, Morris, 1984-1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Western Institutional Review Board (WIRB), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Who's Who in America, 1975-1997 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Widdershoven, Guy, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Wiesing, U., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Wikler, Dan, 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 36-37)
    - Wilcox, Lynn, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Winters, Barbara, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Winters, Betsy, 1973-1992 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Wisner, Katherine, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Wolf, Lesley, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Wolfson, Steven, 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Wolfson, Susan, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Woods Hole, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Woodward, Barbara, Undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - World Association of Medical Editors (WAME), 1998 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - World Medical Association (WMA), 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 48-50)
    - Wustrack, Karl, 1967-1990 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Wyngaarden, James, 1966-1988 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Yale Health Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Yale-New Haven Hospital rules and regulations, 1982-1996 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Yale University policy, 1982-2000 (Box 18, Folder 55-56)
    - Yale University Press, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 57-58)
    - Yamanouchi, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Yawn, Barbara, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Yessian, Mark, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Yotopoulos-Marangopoulis, Alice, 1988-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Younger, Stuart, 1990-1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Zelen, Marvin, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Zelterman, Daniel, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Zhang, Ju, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Zito, Donna, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Zonana, Howard, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Medical ethics course materials
    - Farley-Levine, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Investigative Medicine Program, Yale: Practical and Ethical Issues in Clinical Investigation, 2001 September 19-December 12 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Editorial files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research
    - Ackerman, Terry, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Martin, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Amdur, Robert, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5-6)
    - Annotations, 1988-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Appelbaum, Paul, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Responses, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bankert, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Baylis, Francoise, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Beauchamp, Tom L., 1976-1994 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Benbasset, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Chairman of the Editorial Board, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Christakis, Nicholas, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Cohen, Peter, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Cote, Pat, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Crigger, Bette, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Daugherty, Chris, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Arlene, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Dena, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - DeRenzo, Euan, 1990-1999 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dommel, William, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Dresser, Rebecca, 1981, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Dubler, N., 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Durfee, Sharon, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Eckenwiler, Lisa, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Freedman, Benjamin (Benjie), 1987-1993 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Flagel, David, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Gabriele, Edward, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Glass, Kathleen, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 32-33)
    - Gordon, Bruce, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 34-35)
    - Green, Ronald, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Hall, Jacqulyn Kay, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Hammerschmidt, Dale, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Hastings grant application, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Hastings subcontract, 1979-1999 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Hayes, Gregory J., 1994-1998 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Heath, Erica, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Herrara, C. D., 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hill, George, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Hochhauser, Mark, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Howarth, Marna, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Ideas for articles, 1979-1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Imiprop, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Katz, Susan, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Keehley, Jay, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Kopelman, Loretta, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Kornetsky, Susan, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Landrum, Eric, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Lapham, Sandra, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Lebacqz, Karen, 1979-1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Lederberg, Marguerite, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Lemmens, Trudo, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Levine, Carol, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Levine, Robert and Louis Lasagna, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Levy, Gerhard, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Ludbrook, Philip, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Marquis, Don, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Marshall, Patti, 1991-2001 (Box 21, Folder 22-24)
    - Mattison, Debra, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - McCarthy, Charles, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Meinert, Curtis, 1977-1998 (Box 21, Folder 27-28)
    - Merz, Jon, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Meslin, Eric, 1985-1993 (Box 21, Folder 30-31)
    - Miller, Franklin, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - New [issue of journal], 2000 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Nicholson, R. H., 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - O'Brien, Richard, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Obituaries, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Oldham, Robert K., 1991 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Portello, Ruth, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 37A)
    - Porter, Joan, 1991-1995 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Posever, Thomas, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Post, Stephen, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Powell, Joan, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Powers, Madison, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Prentice, Ernest D., 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Pritchard, Ivor A., 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Publicity, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Pullman, Daryl, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Purtilo, Ruth, 1983-1993 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
    - Rackoff, Jonathan, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Reed, Joyce, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Reilly, Philip, 1980-1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Resnick, David, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Riis, Povl, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Laura, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Rogers, Audrey, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Roizen, Ron, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Rothenberg, Karen, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Schaffner, Ken, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Sheehe, Paul, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Shimm, David, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Sieber, Joan, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Smith, David, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Somerville, Margaret, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Sprumont, Dominique, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Stein, Gary, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Straus, Marc, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Subscription list, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Swazey, Judith, 1979-1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Pittsburgh Conference, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Szebik, Imre, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Tandy, Marlene, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Tignor, Greg, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Twomey, John, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Vawter, Dorothy, 1991-1995 (Box 22, Folder 32)